

ASHWINI K

SENIOR CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

PROFILE

Creative professional with 7 years of extensive experience in customer support and business development. Rapidly adapt and respond to changes in the environment. Currently working as a Sr. Customer Support Executive in E-commerce company called Wecool Imports & Trading Pvt Ltd

CONTACT

- 8884356727
- 8746948550
- ashwinikrishna984@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT, BANGALORE UNIVERSITTY IN 2012 TO 2015 AGGREGATIVE OF 61%

EXPERIENCE

SR. CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

WECOOL IMPORTS & TRADING PVT LTD. SEPTEMBER 2018 to PRESENT

- > Handle business Calls, Emails and Chats individually.
- > Discussing with the customer who called for products enquiry. Explaining about the products and converting them to purchase our products.
- Convincing the unsatisfied customers and to modify negative review to positive from them.
- Making outbound calls to the customers for getting positive reviews for the assigned products.
- Crosscheck with warranty policy of the customers and to do the replacement for defective products.
- > Tracking the ratings and reviews for the products which has assigned.
- Checking the customers post in social media like Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Google & YouTube and replaying accordingly.
- Should prepare the daily, weekly and monthly reports of positive reviews and replacement done.

CUSTOMER CARE EXECUTIVE AND RECEPTIONIST

NRR HOSPIAL | AUGUST 2016 to AUGUST 2018

- > Attending the walk-in customers and to guide them in a proper manner.
- > Answering telephonic calls and e-mail inquiries in a timely basis.
- > Fixing the appointment for the costumers with the doctor.
- > Advising members of the patent to clear the outstanding payment.
- > Also taken care of billing counter if needed.

BEAUTY ADVISOR

BANJARA'S | APRIL 2015 to MARCH 2016

- > Attending the walk-in customers who enters the mart,
- > Influence customer to purchase the beauty products of Banjara's.
- Guiding the customers about beauty concepts and benefits of the products.
- Making telephonic calls and e-mail inquiries to promote beauty products of Banjara's.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Father's name : Krishnappa KV
Date of Birth : 13/03/1994
Gender : Female

Languages Known : Kannada, English, Telugu, and Hindi.